Guide to the Collection of Aerial Photographs 1935-2001
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Aerial Photographs and Orthophotos, 1935-2000; Series II
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-01; GS-CJ (Box 094)
    Line 2
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-11; GS-CJ (Box 094)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 44-91 thru 44-149
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-01; GS-CJ (Box 094)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 47-51 thru 47-140
    Line 3
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-01; GS-CJ (Box 094)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 44-150 thru 55-165
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-01; GS-CJ (Box 095)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 44-166 thru 44-199
    Line 4
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-01; GS-CJ (Box 095)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 45-02 thru 45-51
    Line 5
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-01; GS-CJ (Box 095)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 45-52 thru 45-67
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-01; GS-CJ (Box 095)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 45-68 thru 45-89
    Line 6
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-01; GS-CJ (Box 096)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 45-90 thru 45-121
    Line 15
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-05; GS-CJ (Box 096)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 45-123 thru 45-169
    Line 16
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-05; GS-CJ (Box 096)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 45-170 thru 45-186
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-05; GS-CJ (Box 096)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 45-187 thru 45-208
    Line 14
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-05; GS-CJ (Box 097)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 46-02 thru 46-24
    Line 10
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-05; GS-CJ (Box 097)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 46-25 thru 46-39
    Line 13
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-05; GS-CJ (Box 097)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 46-40 thru 46-60
    Line 12
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-05; GS-CJ (Box 097)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 46-61 thru 46-81
    Line 11
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-11; GS-CJ (Box 098)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 46-96 thru 46-167
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-11; GS-CJ (Box 098)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 46-168 thru 46-196
    Line 9
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-11; GS-CJ (Box 098)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 47-03 thru 47-15
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-11; GS-CJ (Box 098)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 47-16 thru 47-31
    Line 8
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-11; GS-CJ (Box 098)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 47-32 thru 47-50
    Line 7
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-11; GS-CJ (Box 098)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 47-141 thru 47-213
  - Mt. Baker, Eastern Whatcom County, Washington, 1950-08-17; GS-LK (Box 099)
  - Mt. Baker Air Photo Index, 1956-08-13; EBK (Box 099)
  - Mt. Baker Air Photo Index, 1956-08-19; EBK (Box 099)
  - Mt. Baker Air Photo Index, 1956-08-22; EBK (Box 099)
  - Mt. Baker Air Photo Index, 1956-09-03; EBK (Box 099)
  - Mt. Baker Air Photo Index, 1956-09-05; EBK (Box 099)
  - Mt. Baker Air Photo Index, 1956-09-05; EBK (Box 099)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 6
  - Mt. Baker Air Photo Index, 1956-09-05; EBK (Box 099)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 7
  - Mt. Baker Air Photo Index, 1956-09-06; EBK (Box 099)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 8
  - Jefferson County, Alabama, 1967-11-16; CPM (Box 100)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3JJ 240-241
    See also: Box 110.
  - Chichot County, Arkansas, 1951-04-04; CFF (Box 100)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CFF-3H-173
    Scale: 1:21,000
  - Chichot County, Arkansas, 1951-04-04; CFF (Box 100)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CFF-3H-174, 175
  - Chichot County, Arkansas, 1955-11-03; CFF (Box 100)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CFF-1P-126
  - Chichot County, Arkansas, 1955-11-03; CFF (Box 100)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CFF-1P-127, 128
  - Santa Clara County, California, 1950-04-01; CIV (Box 100)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CIV-17G-94, 95, 96
  - Santa Clara County, California, 1956-06-09; CIV (Box 100)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CIV-6R-43
  - Santa Clara County, California, 1956-06-09; CIV (Box 100)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CIV-6R-44, 45
  - Weld County, Colorado, 1950-08-01; YB (Box 101)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: YB-6G-17
  - Weld County, Colorado, 1950-08-01; YB (Box 101)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: YB-6G-18, 19
  - Fairfield County, Connecticut, 1951-09-08; DPD (Box 101)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DPD-7H-109
  - Fairfield County, Connecticut, 1951-09-08; DPD (Box 101)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DPD-7H-110
  - Polk County, Florida, 1952-01-07; CTU (Box 101)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CTU-7H-40
  - Polk County, Florida, 1952-01-07; CTU (Box 101)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CTU-7H-41, 42
  - Walton County, Georgia, 1955-04-30; ATS (Box 101)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ATS-6P-57
  - Walton County, Georgia, 1955-04-30; ATS (Box 101)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ATS-6P-58, 59
  - Boone County, Illinois, 1967-09-25; CG (Box 101)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CG-1HH-123
  - Boone County, Illinois, 1967-09-25; CG (Box 101)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CG-1HH-124
  - Boone County, Illinois, 1967-09-25; CG (Box 101)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CG-1HH-125
  - Cook County, Illinois, 1967-09-11; BWQ (Box 101)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BWQ-1HH-88
  - Cook County, Illinois, 1967-09-11; BWQ (Box 101)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BWQ-1HH-89
  - Lake County, Indiana, 1965-07-15; BFJ (Box 102)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BFJ-1FF-48
  - Lake County, Indiana, 1965-07-15; BFJ (Box 102)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BFJ-1FF-49
  - Lake County, Indiana, 1965-07-15; BFJ (Box 102)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BFJ-1FF-122
  - Lake County, Indiana, 1965-07-15; BFJ (Box 102)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BFJ-1FF-123
  - Baltimore, Maryland, 1957-09-25; AJO (Box 102)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AJO-5T-123
  - Baltimore, Maryland, 1957-09-25; AJO (Box 102)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AJO-5T-124
  - Baltimore, Maryland, 1957-09-25; AJO (Box 102)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AJO-5T-125
  - Baltimore, Maryland, 1957-09-25; AJO (Box 102)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AJO-5T-126
  - Hampshire County, Massachusettss, 1952-06-18; DPB (Box 102)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DPB-6H-110
  - Hampshire County, Massachusetts, 1952-06-18; DPB (Box 102)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DPB-6H-111, 112
  - Suffolk County, Massachusetts, 1952-08-24; DPU (Box 102)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DPU-8K-79
  - Suffolk County, Massachusetts, 1952-08-24; DPU (Box 102)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DPU-8K-80
  - Suffolk County, Massachusetts, 1952-08-24; DPU (Box 102)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DPU-8K-81
  - Suffolk County, Massachusetts, 1952-08-24; DPU (Box 102)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DPU-8K-82
  - Wayne County, Michigan, 1957-05-16; XU (Box 103)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: XU-1P-131
  - Wayne County, Michigan, 1957-05-16; XU (Box 103)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: XU-1P-132
  - Wayne County, Michigan, 1957-05-16; XU (Box 103)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: XU-2P-103
  - Wayne County, Michigan, 1957-06-03; XU (Box 103)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: XU-2P-134
  - Le Seur County, Minnesota, 1958-07-06; WF (Box 103)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: WF-2V-37
  - Le Seur County, Minnesota, 1958-07-06; WF (Box 103)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: WF-2V-38
  - St. Peters, Nicollet County, Minnesota, 1958-07-06; WF (Box 103)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: WF-2V-50
  - St. Peters, Nicollet County, Minnesota, 1957-07-06; WF (Box 103)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: WF-2V-51
  - Sunflower County, Mississippi, 1956-12-01; AVL (Box 103)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AVL-2T-147
  - Sunflower County, Mississippi, 1956-12-01; AVL (Box 103)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AVL-2T-148, 149
  - Hill County, Montana, 1953-09-13; AZR (Box 103)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AZR-5N-197
  - Hill County, Montana, 1953-09-13; AZR (Box 103)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AZR-5N-198
  - Prince George County, Maryland, 1957-06-11; AHV (Box 104)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AHV-1T (various odd numbers from 3-163)
  - Montgomery County, Maryland, 04-15-1957 and 04-30-1957; NV (Box 104)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: NV-3T and 4T (various numbers)
    See also: Box 111.
  - Montgomery County, Maryland, 04-30-1957 and 05-25-1957; NV (Box 104)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: NV-4T and NV-5T (various numbers)
  - Coos County, New Hampshire, 1955-08-04; DXU (Box 104)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DXU-4N-67
  - Coos County, New Hampshire, 1955-08-04; DXU (Box 104)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DXU-4N-68
  - Coos County, New Hampshire, 1955-08-04; DXU (Box 104)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DXU-4N-69
  - Atlantic County, New Jersey, 1963-06-25; CMT (Box 104)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CMT-2DD-222
  - Atlantic County, New Jersey, 1963-06-25; CMT (Box 104)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CMT-2DD-223
  - Atlantic County, New Jersey, 1963-06-25; CMT (Box 104)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CMT-2DD-224
  - Cumberland County, New Jersey, 1956-09-09; CMW (Box 104)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CMW-8R-8
  - Cumberland County, New Jersey, 1956-09-09; CMW (Box 104)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CMW-8R-9, 10
  - Monroe County, New York, 1951-10-03; ARK (Box 105)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ARK-1H-95
  - Monroe County, New York, 1951-10-03; ARK (Box 105)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ARK-1H-96, 97
  - Steuben County, New York, 1964-10-30; ARR (Box 105)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ARR-8EE-39
  - Steuben County, New York, 1964-10-30; ARR (Box 105)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ARR-8EE-40
  - Guilford County, North Carolina, 1965-12-04; ACL (Box 105)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ACL-2HH-112
  - Guilford County, North Carolina, 1965-12-04; ACL (Box 105)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ACL-2HH-113
  - Guilford County, North Carolina, 1965-12-04; ACL (Box 105)
  - Guilford County, North Carolina, 1965-12-04; ACL (Box 105)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ACL-2HH-114
  - Bottineau County, North Dakota, 1953-07-09; BAH (Box 105)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BAH-4M-7
  - Bottineau County, North Dakota, 1953-07-09; BAH (Box 105)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BAH-4M-8, 9
  - Cuyahoga County, Ohio, 1959-07-10; PZ (Box 105)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: PZ-1W-145
  - Cuyahoga County, Ohio, 1959-07-10; PZ (Box 105)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: PZ-1W-146
  - Cuyahoga County, Ohio, 1959-07-10; PZ (Box 105)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: PZ-1W-148
  - Cuyahoga County, Ohio, 1959-07-10; PZ (Box 105)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: PZ-1W-149
  - Cuyahoga County, Ohio, 1959-07-10; PZ (Box 105)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: PZ-1W-145 thru 151
  - Youngstown, Ohio, 1965-10-17; QH (Box 106)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: QH-3FF-110
  - Youngstown, Ohio, 1965-10-17; QH (Box 106)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: QH-3FF-111
  - Youngstown, Ohio, 1965-10-17; QH (Box 106)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: QH-3FF-112
  - Lancaster County, Pennsylvania, 1947-06-20; AHG (Box 106)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AHG-4D-72
  - Lancaster County, Pennsylvania, 1947-06-20; AHG (Box 106)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AHG-4D-73
  - Dallas County, Texas, 1957-11-26; DJU (Box 106)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DJU-1P-221
  - Dallas County, Texas, 1957-11-26; DJU (Box 106)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DJU-1P-222
  - Dallas County, Texas, 1958-01-07; DJU (Box 106)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DJU-4P-167
  - Dallas County, Texas, 1958-01-07; DJU (Box 106)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DJU-4P-168
  - Dallas County, Texas, 1958-01-24; DJU (Box 106)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DJU-5P-54
  - Dallas County, Texas, 1958-01-24; DJU (Box 106)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DJU-5P-55
  - Dallas County, Texas, 1958-02-07; DJU (Box 106)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DJU-5P-122
  - Randall County, Texas, 1953-01-29; DAS (Box 107)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DAS-1M-201
  - Randall County, Texas, 1953-01-29; DAS (Box 107)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DAS-1M-202, 203
  - Danville, Virginia, 1963-09-17; DGG (Box 107)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DGG-7DD-150
  - Danville, Virginia, 1963-09-17; DGG (Box 107)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DGG-7DD-151
  - Danville, Virginia, 1963-09-17; DGG (Box 107)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DGG-7DD-152
  - Prince George County, Maryland, 1957-06-16; AHV (Box 107)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AHV-2T
  - Prince George County, Maryland, 1957-06-16; AHV (Box 107)
  - Prince George County, Maryland, 1957-06-16; AHV (Box 107)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AHV-3T
  - Prince George County, Maryland, 1957-06-16; AHV (Box 107)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AHV-5T
  - Suffolk County, Massachusetts, 1952-08-24; DPQ (Box 107)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DPQ-8K-78 thru 82
    See also: Box 102.
  - Suffolk County, Massachusetts, 1952-08-24; DPQ (Box 107)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DPQ-8K-122 thru 125
  - Clinton County, Michigan, 1938-06-09; BDJ (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BDJ-3-various
    Road map of area in folder, no flight lines.
  - Clinton County, Michigan, 1964-06-16; BDJ (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BDJ-1EE and BDJ-2EE
  - Kalamazoo, Michigan, 1967-09-02; BDW (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BDW-3HH-200 ,201 ,202
  - Detroit, Wayne County, Michigan, 1957-05-16; XU (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: XU-1P
    See also: Box 103.
  - Detroit, Wayne County, Michigan, 1957-05-16; XU (Box 108)
  - Detroit, Wayne County, Michigan, 1957-05-16; XU (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: XU-3P-33
  - Brown County, Minnesota, 1968-09-11; BIQ (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BIQ-14HH-211, 212- 213
  - Hennepin County, Minnesota, 1964-10-14; WN (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: WN-2EE-100 thru 103
  - Minnesota (Various), 1958-07-06; WE (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: WE-2V and WE-3V
  - Ramsey County and St. Peter's County, Minnesota, 11-13-1956 and 10-05-1957; WE; WO (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: WE-1R and W0-2T
  - Neshoba County, Mississippi, 1966-01-08; AVB (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AVB-1GG-179, 180, 181
  - St. Louis County, Missouri, 1958-05-13; TQ (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: TQ-1T-34 thru 38
  - Carson Sink, Churchill County, Nevada, 11/21/1956 and 11/25/1956; VV HY M2 AMS; VV HY M3 AMS (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 288 thru 294, 341 thru 344; 528 thru 532, 540 thru 547
  - Big Smoky Valley, Esmeralda County, Nevada, 10/14/1952 and 1954; VV HU M 10, 91, 120, 121 AMS (Box 108)
  - Cresent Valley, Eureka County, Nevada, Undated (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 8986, 8987, 9559, 9560
  - Pahrump Valley, Nye County, Nevada, Oct. 1952; VV HU M5 AMS (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 296 thru 302
  - Newark Valley, White Pine County, Nevada, Undated (Box 108)
  - Atlantic County, New Jersey, 1963-06-25; CMT (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CMT-2DD-221 thru 224
    See also: Box 104.
  - Trenton, Mercer County, New Jersey, 1963-05-07; CMZ (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CMZ-3DD-63 thru 64
  - Steuben County, New York, 1964-10-30; ARR (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ARR-8EE-37 thru 40
    See also: Box 105.
  - Buncombe County, North Carolina, 1963-10-05; DNE (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DNE-4EE-219 thru 222
  - Catawba County, North Carolina, 1956-02-26; BOQ (Box 108)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BOQ-1P
  - Catawba County, North Carolina, 1956-03-10; BOQ (Box 109)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BOQ-2P
  - Catawba County, North Carolina, 1956-03-23; BOQ (Box 109)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BOQ-3P
  - Cleveland County, North Carolina, 1956-01-14; ACG (Box 109)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ACG-1P
  - Cleveland County, North Carolina, 1956-01-14; ACG (Box 109)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ACG-2P
  - Cleveland County, North Carolina, 1956-01-15; ACG (Box 109)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ACG-3P
  - Guilford County, North Carolina, 1966-12-04; ACL (Box 109)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ACL-2HH-112 thru 115
  - Willmington, New Hanover County, North Carolina, 1984-12-15 (Box 109)
    See also: Box 112 for Wilmington Area, NC.
  - Willmington, New Hanover County, North Carolina, 1984-12-15 (Box 109)
  - Moorehead City, Carteret County, North Carolina, 1984-12-16; 213.54 (Box 110)
  - Surf City, Carteret County, North Carolina, 1984-12-15; 213.54 (Box 110)
  - Core Banks, Carteret County, North Carolina, 1984-12-16; 213.54 (Box 110)
  - Jefferson County, Alabama, 1967-11-16; CPM (Box 110)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3JJ and 4JJ
    See also: Box 100.
  - Mobile County, Alabama, 1960-11-02; CPU (Box 110)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CPU-1BB-36 thru 43
  - Macon County, Alabama, 1954-12-22; HL (Box 110)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: HL-4N-97
  - Fairbanks, Alaska, circa 1941 (Box 110)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-2011
  - Holbrook, Arizona (Box 110)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2266 and 2267; 2309 thru 2315
  - Harper Lake area, California, 1954-07-01; VV FS M1 AMS (Box 110)
  - Silver Lake, California, 1954-02-24; VV HU M17 AMS (Box 110)
  - Dale Lake, California, 1954-12-16; VV FS M69 AMS (Box 110)
  - Denver, Jefferson County, Colorado, 1955-06-28; AIN (Box 110)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AIN-1N-70 thru 77
  - Denver, Jefferson County, Colorado, 1955-07-02; AIN (Box 110)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AIN-2N-10 thru 16
  - Bridgeport, Fairchild County, Connecticut, 1963-07-06; DPD (Box 110)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DPD-5DD 2 thru 4
  - Bridgeport, Fairchild County, Connecticut, 1963-08-15; DPD (Box 110)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DPD-6DD 100 thru 103
  - Orange County, Florida, 1954-03-01; DEVA (Box 110)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DEVA-2M, 3M (Various)
  - Pasco County, Florida, 1968-01-20; CTT (Box 110)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CTT-1JJ 246 thru 248
  - St. Johns County, Florida, 1960-05-14; CZA (Box 110)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CZA-3AA-94 thru 96
  - Atlanta, Fulton County, Georgia, 1960-02-23; ATJ (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ATJ-4AA-163 thru 171
  - Athens, Clark County, Georgia, 1967-02-13; ATG (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ATG-5HH-174 thru178
  - Chicago, Cook County, Illinois, 1967-09-11; BWQ (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BWQ-1HH-86 thru 89
    See also: Box 101.
  - Chicago, Cook County, Illinois, 1961-11-07; BWQ (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BWQ-2AA-(various)
  - Peoria County, Illinois, 1963-08-14; BXF (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BXF-2DD-269 thru 271
  - St. Clair County, Illinois, 1968-09-02; SK (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: SK-1JJ-(various)
  - St. Clair County, Illinois, 1968-09-20; SK (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: SK-3JJ-111 thru 113
  - Lake County, Indiana, 1965-07-15; BFJ (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BFJ-1FF-(Various)
  - Vincennes, Know County, Indiana, 1966-10-07; QQ (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: QQ-5GG-116 thru 118
  - Iowa County, Iowa, 1963-08-03; DH (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DH-2DD-32 thru 34
  - Waterloo, Blackhawk County, Iowa, 1964-08-10; ST (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ST-1EE-209 thru 211
  - Selma, Dallas County, Alabama, 1965-10-24; EH (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: EH-3GG-128 thru 131
  - Owensboro, Kentucky, 1964-07-15 (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: S4407 and S4408
  - Baltimore, Ann Arundel County, Maryland, 1957; AHR (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AHR-2T thru AHR-5T (Various)
  - Baltimore, Baltimore County, Maryland, 1957-09-25; AJO (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AJO-4T-(Various)
  - Baltimore, Baltimore County, Maryland, 1957-09-25; AJO (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AJO-5T-(Various)
  - Baltimore, Baltimore County, Maryland, 1957-09-27; AJO (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AJO-6T-(Various)
  - Baltimore, Baltimore County, Maryland, 1957-10-03; AJO (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AJO-7T-(Various)
  - Baltimore County, Maryland, 1964-05-18; AJO (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AJO-1DD-202 thru 205
  - Montgomery County, Maryland, 1957-04-11; NV (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: NV-1T-(Various)
  - Montgomery County, Maryland, 1957-04-15; NV (Box 111)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: NV-2T-(Various)
  - Gaston County, North Carolina, 1956-01-09; ACK (Box 112)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ACK-1P-(Various)
  - Gaston County, North Carolina, 1956-01-15; ACK (Box 112)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ACK-3P-(Various)
  - Gaston County, North Carolina, 1956-01-09; ACK (Box 112)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ACK-4P-(Various)
  - Lincoln County, North Carolina, 1956-01-09; ACN (Box 112)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ACN-1P-(Various)
  - Lincoln County, North Carolina, 1956-01-14; ACN (Box 112)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ACN-2P-(Various)
  - Lincoln County, North Carolina, 1956-01-15; ACN (Box 112)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ACN-3P-(Various)
  - Lincoln County, North Carolina, 1956-03-04; ACN (Box 112)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ACN-4P-(Various)
  - Willmington, New Hanover County, North Carolina, 1956-03-23; AOQ (Box 112)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AOQ-1N-(Various)
    See also: Box 109 for Wilmington Area, NC.
  - Willmington, New Hanover County, North Carolina, 1956-03-23; AOQ (Box 112)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AOQ-2N-(Various)
  - Willmington, New Hanover County, North Carolina, 1956-03-25; AOQ (Box 112)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AOQ-3N-(Various)
  - Rutherford County, North Carolina, 1956-03-05; BOS (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BOS-1P-(Various)
  - Rutherford County, North Carolina, 03-05-1956 and 03-09-1956; BOS (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BOS-2P-(Various)
  - Rutherford County, North Carolina, 1956-03-09; BOS (Box 113)
  - Rutherford County, North Carolina, 1956-03-05; BOS (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BOS-3P-(Various)
    Some mis-labelled 'BOR', but are in sequence with other BOS photos.
  - Rutherford County, North Carolina, 1956-04-09; BOS; BOU (Box 113)
    Two BOU photos in back of folder: BOU-3P-48 and 217.
  - Biggs Junction, Oregon, 1967-08-15 (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: L4687 and L4688
  - Montgomery County, Maryland, 1957-04-15; NP (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: NP-2T and NP-3T
  - Port Orford, Oregon, Undated (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3 Oblique views
  - Willamette National Forest, Oregon, 1967-09-16; FFP18-7-2; Olympus Aerial Surveys (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-61 thru 1-664
  - Pittsburg, Allegheny County, Pennsylvania, 1967-05-26; APS (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: APS-1HH-153 thru 155
  - Charleston, Charleston County, South Carolina, 1963-11-08; CDV (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: CDV-4EE-115 thru 119
    See also:cludes 1 color photo which looks to be more recent.
  - Dallas County, Texas, 1957 and 1958; DJU (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DJU-1P, 4P, 5P (Various)
    See also: Box 106.
  - Alexandria, Virginia, 1960-04-15; 23871 (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 38 and 39